Let's go over the mission one last time.
At 1300 hours,
each squad will take helicopters to their
designated mountain-entry points.
They will then spend a night
wiping out any Savages they encounter
and return to base
at 1700 hours tomorrow.
That's all well and good...
But what's with these team assignments?
It's an honor to be in
the same team as you, Emilia-sama!
We must be connected by fate!
No, we're not!
Also, I'm Emile!
Kisaragi Hayato!
I played along with you yesterday,
but we're going into battle for real today.
During this mission, I'm going to
prove to you how superior I am!
"Played along"? You're the one who started it...
Claudia Loetty.
Wh-What is it?
I understand that you would like to take
Emile Crossfode back to your country,
but he is a valuable asset to the Little Garden,
and an important crewmate of ours.
President...
If he insists on staying
at the Little Garden,
then we will do everything we can
to keep him there.
Why did you say that now?
We're going into battle together,
so I wanted to let you know what I'm thinking.
I trust we're on the same page?
Fine, I understand!
I'm not that irresponsible!
Hayato, Emile!
President, we've come
to see you before we sortie.
Thank you.
You're in Squad F, correct?
Yes. Us and two women, Ally and Wendy.
Basically, as long as we don't
run into any Savages,
I get to enjoy my own
personal harem to the fullest.
Ouch!
What do you mean, "harem"?!
I was just kidding! It was a joke.
Okay. Understood.
The helicopters are ready.
Everyone, please head out.
Liu Xuemei, although you'll
be staying behind here,
you're a Little Garden Slayer.
We're counting on your backup.
R-Right!
It's time.
Night at the Lake
You're finished!
We can't let her hog the spotlight.
Yeah.
We got one.
I'll go.
Stand there and watch me, Kisaragi Hayato!
Hundred On!
So that's her Hundred, huh?
Yeah. Claudia wants to show off,
so how about we watch her?
Take this!
Tudor Rose!
Emilia-sama, finish it off!
Why me?
Hurry up! This is our chance!
G-Got it...
Hundred On!
We did it!
That's my Emilia-sama!
I told you, I'm Emile!
Don't you think I'm more useful
than Kisaragi Hayato?
We worked together seamlessly just now, too.
Is that why you had me
land the finishing blow?
That's right!
It's the first time we've worked together!
You know...
Birds of a feather...
I can't find any other Savages
in the area except for these two.
We've just started.
We're going to take out as many Savages as possible
until we leave the mountain tomorrow.
Right.
Look at them go.
There are so many Slayers
and Savages in one spot.
A mountain of treasure.
Leave the rest to me!
Rocket Knuckles!
You're good, Reitia.
You too, Ally.
That makes two.
But the two of them are
using up too much energy.
They need to make it last.
Yeah.
We've got a long road ahead of us.
Everything's going smoothly, Claire-sama.
Yes.
We're doing better than expected,
having taken out five already.
Kisaragi Hayato hasn't landed
the finishing blow on any yet.
Here, Emilia-sama. Open up.
That's because you're taking
all the good stuff for yourself, Claudia.
But...
I'm fine.
I don't mind just doing damage
or acting as a decoy.
How gallant of you.
Trying to act cool!
Claire-sama,
it sounds as if there are
going to be showers tonight.
I see...
I doubt light rain will pose
much of a problem,
but we'll have to be careful with
beam weapons, of course.
We're going to split into two groups
and take turns getting four hours of sleep.
The group that's awake will secure
the perimeter and keep watch.
Understood?
I want to be with Hayato!
Hey, Emile!
Everyone, go to sleep.
Emile Crossfode,
it's dangerous for you two
be alone together!
Get away from him!
What?
That's right!
Kisaragi Hayato's the only guy here.
He can't be alone with anyone!
I'm a guy, too!
So Emilia-sama and I will team up!
Why?
Emilia-sama, be gentle.
It makes sense for the two guys
to group together, Hayato and me.
Do you really think you'll be able
to use that excuse here?
Denied.
Why am I with the vice president
instead of Hayato?
What's done is done.
Anyway, let's get the fire going before
it starts to rain and our kindling gets wet.
Blah.
I... I can't sleep.
Kisaragi Hayato.
Y-Yes?
Getting sleep is also part of your mission.
You can't call yourself a good Slayer
without being able to do that.
Right.
Everything is quiet.
There was a shower earlier,
but it ended quickly.
According to HQ,
we've taken out 42 Savages in total.
There are more Savages here than estimated.
We need to be even more on guard, then.
We'll rest now.
Let's go, Emile Crossfode.
W-Wait!
Hayato, let's talk a lot later!
Sure.
Good night, Emilia-sama!
It's Emile!
The stars are nice.
Yes. Karen—
My sister would have loved it.
You sure care about your sister.
It's just us two siblings.
She's sick and can't travel all over.
Siblings, huh?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...
I don't mind.
I hope we can make it a world
where everyone can relax and look up
at the sky, like we are now.
That's why we're fighting.
Excuse me...
I'm sorry to bug you two
while you're getting cozy.
Wh-What is it, Claudia Loetty?
Nothing, but with you two
looking up at the stars like that,
it reminds me of a
romantic scene out of a movie.
Th-That's not what...
Anyway, I think I saw
a pretty large shadow
moving over towards the lake.
Was it just my imagination?
A large shadow?
I was thinking there could be
a Savage over there.
How about you two check it out?
We should?
I'll stay here.
If there's an emergency,
I'll wake up Emilia-sama and Erica
and take care of things here.
Understood.
If there's nothing there,
since you're already by the lake,
why not go on a date
while you're at it?
I won't bug you,
so feel free to get as cozy as you want.
D-Don't be ridiculous!
L-Let's go, Kisaragi Hayato.
This isn't a date.
We're only patrolling the area.
S-Sure.
Be careful, you two!
Looks like it went well.
It seems the queen is interested
in Kisaragi Hayato.
If the two of them get lovey-dovey,
I can get Emilia-sama back to Gudenburg.
Just as Claudia said.
Yes.
This is Claire. Come in, Claudia Loetty.
A transmission error?
It'd be bad if we went back and lost it.
If there's just one of them...
We can take care of it right now.
Prez!
Kisaragi Hayato!
That was surprising.
You just tripped out of nowhere.
I... I could have taken care of it
without your help!
But thank you.
I'm grateful.
Your suit is all dirty.
Yeah.
I can't go back like this.
I'd like to wash off first.
I can't sleep.
I want to talk to Hayato just a little bit.
Emilia-sama, over here.
Come on.
Huh? Where are the president and Hayato?
Emilia-sama, I hate to be the one to tell you,
but the two of them
went on a date to the lake.
A-A date?!
H-How is it?
Cold?
No, the geothermal properties
have turned it into a hot spring.
I can clean myself well.
I... I see.
So the president and Hayato
went to the lake together?
I don't really believe it.
It's true.
Emilia-sama, you don't need
to be with that cheater.
Come back to Gudenburg with me.
No.
Why?!
Even if the president
and Hayato get together,
I'm not giving up.
I don't want to run back to my country
just because someone else took Hayato.
B-But...
Have you been able to gain more control
over your Variant power now?
Well, I haven't had any problems while training,
but it hasn't activated in actual combat since
the battle on Zwei Islands, so it's hard to tell.
How does it feel when
your Variant power activates?
I can't really explain it,
but it feels like all your senses
are distant from you.
Time flows slowly....
So she must've experienced that, too.
She?
My sister, Liza.
But she's different from you two.
She's a designer baby.
Savage fluids were injected
into a fertilized egg,
and she was born a Variant.
Did Vitaly do that, too?!
No. That woman was no more than an assistant.
The person in charge of
the project was Linis Harvey.
Our mother.
What do you mean?
Why would you do that to your own child?
My mother said that
it was to beat the gods in war.
Beat the gods in war?
As my mother wished,
Liza exhibited extremely rare—abnormal, even—
talent as a Slayer from a young age.
But one day, she released a forbidden power
in order to save me from a Savage.
Claire!
Ever since then,
Liza's been sleeping like that.
I say "sleeping,"
but her body is, even now,
releasing enough energy
to power the Little Garden.
In other words, Liza is Warslarn's...
My brother Judar's trump card.
The reason why I'm the
Little Garden's captain
is so I can keep an eye on Judar's actions.
Liza isn't a tool for their ambitions.
She's my precious little sister.
How selfish, don't you think?
I act like I'm working
towards some just cause,
but it's really all about my family:
my sister, brother, and mother.
President...
I might be in a position of responsibility,
but I really just want to
protect my little sister.
Kisaragi Hayato.
Do you think that makes me
a failure of a captain?
No. I'm the same way.
If my sister hadn't needed treatment,
I might not have become a Slayer.
I think most people fight for similar reasons.
World peace and justice
are great reasons, too,
but your own personal reasons
and situation are also important.
So I don't think
what you're doing is wrong.
Kisaragi Hayato.
I figured this out after becoming a Slayer.
This power can put smiles on people's faces.
If I can defend someone's smile by fighting,
that's enough reason.
If I can make this world a better place where
everyone's happy and nobody gets hurt...
If that's what you want,
I'm sure your Hundred will give it to you.
Kisaragi Hayato,
would you continue to use your ideals
and your power for the Little Garden?
I'll do everything I can.
What's going on?
It's an emergency call.
Kisaragi Hayato,
you saw my boobs, didn't you?!
And you grabbed them tight...
I... I'm sorry!
Take this!
I-I'll make sure you
take responsibility for this!
This is Kisaragi Hayato from Squad E.
I just got your emergency call.
What's going on?
This is Zayed Huffman from Squad D.
What's going on, Zayed?!
We were just attacked by a three Hunters.
Squad D has been wiped out.
They're attacking all the squads.
Everyone should be on alert.
A-Are you okay?!
Three Hunters...
It has to be the same ones that
appeared on Zwei Islands.
Which means they must be
jamming the communications.
I'm worried about Emile and the others.
Let's get back.
That's Fritz.
It's a signal flare to alert us of danger.
Kisaragi Hayato, get back to the tent and
tell Erica and the rest what's going on.
I'll go help them.
But if you're alone...
No need to worry about me.
I'm the Little Garden's
student council president.
If my fellow students require help,
it is my duty to rush right in.
Understood.
That's too bad for you.
Reinforcements will be
coming any moment now.
How dare you!
You're the only one left.
As you heard, I can't go down
until reinforcements come.
Like you can hold us off.
I'll finish you off in a flash.
Limit out!
Variant mode?
Is that all you have?
Quit running your mouth!
It's over.
I'm taking your Hundred, too.
Who is it?!
How dare you hurt my comrades?
The perfect queen!
And she's in her full-body armament.
So you know me.
It's an honor.
Claire-sama.
I'm sorry I was late, Liddy.
You've done well to stand against them
as long as you did.
I'm sorry.
Please...
I have a question for you all.
Tell me what you know about Vitaly Tynyanov.
Why do you know about Vitaly?!
If you surrender now and provide
information about everything you know,
I can guarantee your safety.
But even if you don't,
you're going to tell me what you know.
That's enough!
You Warslarn lapdog!
Resistance is futile.
Even if you use your Variant power,
it's not as strong as
my full-body armament.
Reinforcements will be coming soon, as well.
Give up, leave the Hundreds
you've taken, and surrender.
Rain?
Nee-chan. Nakri.
It seems luck is on our side.
Dragon Type